<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="api.css"?>
<api>

<section>
	<heading>Module</heading>
	<name>Weather</name>
</section>

<section>
	<heading>Class</heading>
	<name>Temperate</name>
</section>

<section>
	<heading>Synopsis</heading>
	<content>This class allows you to interact with the temperate aspect of the weather.</content>
</section>

<section>
	<heading>Property</heading>
	<property>
		<type>string</type>
		<name>unit</name>
		<description>This variable will control how the weather interprets the temperature, and allows for conversion. Can be either "F", "C", or "K".</description>
	</property>
	<property>
		<type>double</type>
		<name>value</name>
		<description>The numerical value of the temperature. The value can be changed my various methods to convert between units, and can also be directly modified by code.</description>
	</property>
</section>

<section>
	<heading>Method</heading>
	<method>
		<type>double</type>
		<name>toCelcius()</name>
		<description>Will attempt to change value property to the correct Celcius value. Changes the unit property as well. Returns the new value.</description>
	</method>
	<method>
                <type>double</type>
                <name>toFahrenheit()</name>
                <description>Will attempt to change value property to the correct Fahrenheit value. Changes the unit property as well. Returns the new value.</description>
        </method>
	<method>
                <type>double</type>
                <name>toKelvin()</name>
                <description>Will attempt to change value property to the correct Kelvin value. Changes the unit property as well. Returns the new value.</description>
        </method>

</section>

<section>
	<heading>Remark</heading>
	<content>Created by scoutchorton. Based on the following challenge:</content>
	<quote>Implement a function that will accept a numeric argument to represent a temperature value and a string argument to represent a unit of temperature measurement. Temperature arguments should be any integer or real number. Unit argument should include [C]elsius, [F]ahrenheit, and [K]elvin. The function should display the given temperature in each of the other systems. The return value should be true if the conversion was successful and false otherwise.</quote>
</section>

</api>
